这个电台真够烂的
The radio around here sucks.
拜托 老弟
Come on, man.
这个案子可没那么诡异 不是吗
Jobs don't get much weirder than this, you know?
死掉的维克脖子上有咬痕 体内的血也没了
Dead vic with a gnawed-on neck, body drained of blood,
而且证人也证实了那就是如假包换的吸血鬼
and a witness who swears up and down that it was a vampire.
对 我也同意 真是件棘手的案子
No, I … I agree. it's a hell of a case.
有点激情吧
A little more gusto, please.
感觉就快世界末日了
It's just…the world is coming to an end.
事情变得有点复杂 知道吗
Things are a little complicated, you know?
好吧 我们无法拯救世界 至少今天不行
Yeah, well, we can't save the world, not today anyway.
但我们还可以砍下几个吸血鬼的头
But what we can do is chop off some vamps' heads.
打起精神 伙计 就像平时一样
Come on, man, it's like the good old days.
一次真正的怪物猎杀
An honest-to-goodness monster hunt.
终于到了温彻斯特家族重新处理
It's about time the winchesters got back to tackling.
简单上手黑白分明案子的时候了
A straightforward, black-and-white case.
我们还是去看新电影《突袭者》吧
We still got to see the new "raiders" movie.
已经看过了
Saw it.
没和我一起看
Without me?
那时你还在地狱
You were in hell.
那不是借口
That's no excuse.
英式大脆饼
Big pretzel!
谢谢
Thank you.
午安
Guten tag.
"guten tag" yourself.
像是我们要找的人
Looks like that's our man.
治安官迪特里希
Sheriff dietrich.
你们是联邦调查局的
Are you the boys from the fed?
调查员安格斯和杨
Agents angus and young.
我们来调查你的问题
We called ahead about your, uh, problem.
对
Right. um…
我会告诉你们是什么
I'll tell you what,
为什么不去人少点的地方聊聊呢
Why don't we talk this out away from the crowd, huh?
玛丽莎·莱特 26岁
Marissa wright, 26,
刚刚在啤酒节上死于非命
Just up from lockhard for the 'fest.
太惨了 实在太惨了
Terrible. just terrible.
这是小镇在旅游高峰期
It's the last thing.
需要的最后一件事
This town needs at peak tourist season.
也是玛丽莎·莱特需要的
Definitely the last thing marissa wright needed.
这是什么鬼东西
What the hell?
这可把我问住了 我是说
Yeah, you got me … I mean,
凶手是疯子对吗
This killer's some kind of grade-"a" wacko, right?
一些撒旦的狂热者 安妮·赖斯小说的书迷
I mean, some satan-worshipping, anne rice-reading,
哥特小说中的吸血鬼痴迷者
Gothic, psycho vampire wannabe.
治安官 在你的报告中 提到有一名目击者
Sheriff, in your report, you mentioned a witness.
是啊 我希望没有 但目击者坚持作证
Yeah, I wished I didn't. but our witness insisted.
目击者是爱德华 布鲁尔
That's ed brewer.
你们调查的不完全可靠
Not exactly what you'd call reliable.
我记得你
I remember you.
我也记得你
And I remember you…
杰米
"jamie."
我从不忘记漂亮的东西
I never forget a pretty… everything.
我们是来找爱德华 布鲁尔
We're looking for ed brewer.
找爱德华干嘛
What do you want with ed?
我们是
Well, we are, uh…
联邦探员
…federal agents.
布鲁尔先生目击了犯罪过程 我们只是
Mr. brewer was witness to a serious crime. we just.
等一下 你们是联邦探员
Wait a minute. you're a fed?
你看起来一点也不像探员
Wow, you don't come on like a fed.
真的吗
Seriously?
我是独行侠 小姐
I'm a maverick, ma'am.
带徽章的反叛者
A rebel with a badge.
从不拘泥于条条框框之中
One thing I don't play by … the rules.
好吧 独行侠
Okay, maverick.
那么我们可以在哪里找到布鲁尔先生
Um, so, where can we find mr. brewer?
我告诉警察所有看见的事了
I told the cops everything I saw.
没人相信我
No one believes me.
你们又有何不同呢
Why should you be any different?
相信我 布鲁尔先生 我们不一样
Believe me, mr. brewer, we're different.
我对天发誓我说的是实话 现在我倒成了小镇的笑柄
I spoke the god's honest truth, and now I'm the town joke.
玛丽莎·莱特被谋杀 这对我们来说不是玩笑
Marissa wright's murder is no joke to us.
我们想知道所有一切
And we want to hear everything,
无论有多荒诞
No matter how strange it may seem.
我们经历过很多的怪异事件
We have a lot of experience with strange.
午夜过后
It was just after midnight.
我像往常一样离开这里
I just left here, and like I do every night,
穿过回家路上的公园
I cut through the park on the way home.
开始 我以为有对情侣正在接吻
At first, I thought it was a couple kissing.
但她挣扎的厉害
But she was… struggling too much.
而那男的
And this man,
他正在咬女的脖子
He was … well, he was biting her neck.
你可以描述下攻击者的长相吗
Can you describe her assailant?
他是吸血鬼
Oh, he was a vampire.
好吧 那么 你认为
Okay, right. and by that, you mean …
就是所熟知的吸血鬼
You know, a vampire.
他看上去像
So, he looked like.
他看上去像吸血鬼
He looked like a vampire,
有一对尖牙
You know, with the fangs.
向后梳的头发还有一件奇特的斗篷
And the slicked-back hair and the fancy cape.
在绸缎上还有个像奖章一样的东西
And the little medallion thingy on the ribbon.
你是说德古拉（经典的吸血鬼形象）
You mean like a dracula?
不错 很像德古拉
Exactly. like a dracula.
有着非常重的口音
Right down to the accent.
- 口音 - 对
The accent. yep.
他说什么了
What did he say?
类似于
You know, something like…
别动 人类
"stay away, mortal!
夜幕都是属于我的
The night is mine!"
你们相信我吗？
You do believe me, don't you?
他们来这儿肯定是为了那个被谋杀的女人
They must be here following up on that murdered woman.
疯狂的爱德华和他的吸血鬼故事
Crazy ed and his vampire story.
他特怪异 但并不疯狂
He might be weird, but he's not crazy.
你刚才还说
Look, you're just saying that.
你迷倒了那个男孩还给了你20美元小费
'cause the guy has a crush on you and he tips you in $20s.
露西
Lucy.
有没有啤酒喝
So, you got a beer back there for me?
我不清楚 杨探员 你调查完了？
I don't know, agent young. you off duty?
还有一些
And then some.
你怎么想？
So, what do you think?
变态崇拜吸血鬼的哥特人
Goth, psycho vampire wannabe, right?
应该和我们的活没关系
Definitely not our kind of case.
顶 不过谁关心呢
Agreed. but who cares?
房间订好了 现在可是啤酒节
Room's paid for, and it's oktoberfest.
来吧 伙计
Come on, brother.
啤酒还是酒吧女郎
Beer and bar wenches.
漂亮女郎今天反映可不够热情
Pretty sure women today don't react well.
对于做爱这事 迪恩
To the whole "wench" thing, dean.
嗨 小姐 我的啤酒呢
Hey, bar wench, where's that beer?
就来 长官
Coming up, good sir!
伙计 啤酒节啊
Dude, oktoberfest.
啤酒来了
There you go.
你怎么不来一杯
What can I get you?
他可不怎么能喝
Oh, he doesn't drink.
他是个信教的科学家 可不想吃阿司匹林
He's a christian scientist. doesn't even take aspirin.
他正被他的男朋友监视着
He's a real drag on stakeouts.
你真搞笑
You're funny.
我可是还有一肚子的笑料
I'm a lot more than that.
找个你下班的时候我表演给你看
I'd love to get a chance to show you the rest.
什么时候开始？
What time you get off?
哈哈 就像我说的 真搞笑啊
Ha ha. like I said, "funny."
伙计 是时候去做下坏事了
Man, it is time to right some wrongs.
再来一次
Come again?
看着我
Look at me.
我从地狱里出来
I came back from the furnace.
却没有留下任何疤痕 对吧
Without any of my old scars, right?
枪伤 刀伤
You know, bullet wounds, knife cuts,
还有那些个骨折的手指
None of the off-angled fingers from all the breaks.
我的皮现在像婴儿般细腻光滑
I mean, my hide is as smooth as a baby's bottom,
总结来说就一句话
Which leads me to conclude,
悲哀 我还没碰过别人
Sadly… that my virginity is intact.
什么
What?
- 我已经重回了处男之身 - 重
- I have been re-hymenated. - re.
饶了我吧
Please.
迪恩 天使或许可以把你救出地狱
Dean, maybe angels can pull you out of hell,
但没人会干那个
But no one could do that.
老弟 我是重回了处男之身
Brother, I have been re-hymenated.
但作为情场浪子却不需要留着它
And the dude will not abide.
好了 老哥
All right, dude.
那么 你去挥霍你的处男之身
Well, you go do whatever you got to do,
而我则回房去睡我的觉
And I'm gonna go back to the room and get some sleep.
那么 今晚如何
So? How 'bout tonight?
噢 抱歉 我答应了露西今晚是女孩之夜
Oh, sorry. I promised lucy a girls' night out.
此外 没自尊的酒吧女郎
Besides, no self-respecting bar wench.
至少可以自己挑选她的第一次服务的客人
Lets herself get picked up by a customer on the first try.
但是 我不是一个客人 我是一名联邦特工
Well, I'm not a customer. I'm a federal agent.
明天再来吧 联邦警探
Try again tomorrow, g-man.
希望我可以
I wish I could.
- 我想我们会为了这个案子留下来 - 什么意思
- I don't think we're staying on the case. - what?
对你而言它太诡异了
Is it too weird for you?
是不够诡异
Not weird enough.
- 瑞克 你听到了吗 - 什么
- Rick. did you hear that? - what?
这声音听起来象是狼叫
It sounded like a wolf.
拜托 玛丽 别再说这个了
Come on, marie, don't change the subject.
我说过的对一个男人而言什么都可能发生 如果他不
I told you what could happen to a man if he doesn't …
- 这些传说都是假的 - 是的
- Those stories aren't true. - they are.
宝贝儿 如果一个男人无法得到他想要的
Baby, if a man doesn't get the stuff.
特别是在他有正常生理需求 让它忍耐
Out of his system regularly, it can back up.
最终就会导致 医学上的问题
And cause all kinds of… medical-type problems.
嘘 你听到了吗
Shh, do you hear that?
安娜·玛丽 在宾夕法尼亚是没有狼的
Anne marie, there aren't any wolves in pennsylvania.
然后它就只是 只是把瑞克撕成了碎片
And then it just … it just tore rick into little pieces.
小姐 我们了解这有点为难
Ma'am, we understand how hard this is,
但你能具体描述下这个生物吗
But can you describe the creature?
噢
Oh.
那就是一个狼人
It was a werewolf.
狼人
A werewolf?
- 你确定 - 噢 当然
- You're sure? - oh, yeah.
毛茸茸的脸上长着黑黑的鼻子
With the furry face and the black nose.
还有一双利爪以及破碎的裤子和T-恤
And the claws and the torn-up pants and shirt,
和老电影演得一模一样
Like from the old movies.
嗯 好吧
Um, well…
行了 那么
Okay, so…
谢谢你的合作
Thank you for your time.
先是一个德古拉 现在又来一个老电影时代的狼人
First a dracula and now a full-on movie-time wolf man?
这该死的城镇究竟咋啦
What the hell is going on in this town?
噢
Ohh. whew.
见鬼了
Damn!
好吧
All right.
不管这是不是一个精神错了的崇拜者
Whatever did this wasn't a psycho wannabe.
看看这些咬痕
Look at those bite marks.
刚好咬到骨头
Right down to the bone…
或者更深
And deeper.
力量大到足以将常人的四肢撕下来
Strong enough to tear a healthy man apart limb from limb.
极可能是狼人
Could be a werewolf.
是的 除非 瞧
Yeah, except, look.
心脏的碎片也在这儿
The heart's still there in one piece.
他们重来不会剩下心脏
They never leave the heart behind.
所以我不停地问 这他妈的究竟是怎么回事
Thus I reiterate … what the hell is going on?
我希望你们两个可以告诉我
Well, I was hoping you boys could tell me.
我刚刚从化验室拿到他们赶出来的结果
I just got a rush job back from the lab.
在尸体上我们发现了一些纤维
On those fibers we found on the body.
犬齿 狼的毛发
Canine. wolf hairs.
我头很痛
I'm getting a headache.
我想不通 伙计
I don't know, man.
看来我们失败在不看午夜场
Looks like we've stumbled on to a midnight showing.
比如「德古拉会见狼人」
Of "dracula meets wolf man."
是那出吗
Is that it?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我意思是 狼人看起来确实是真的
I mean, wolf man seems real enough.
我想它也让德古拉真实多了
It makes dracula seem a little less impossible, I guess.
对 但是狼人是不长狼毛的
Yeah, but werewolves don't grow wolf hair.
- 那只一个神话故事 - 是的
- That's just a myth. - yeah.
那么 要干什么 我们是到了一个有吸血鬼
So, what? we've got a vampire.
和狼人怪物作怪的城镇吗
And a werewolf monster mashing this town?
看来你们还会多待一会儿
Looked like you guys are staying a while.
我听说了瑞克·迪肯的事
I heard about rick deacon.
是啊 这个案子开始变得十分诡异了
Yeah, this case just got weird enough.
对我们这个部门而言
For, uh, our department.
好吧 啤酒算我的
Well, beers are on me.
还有 就像你知道的 我今天午夜下班
And, just so you know, I get off at midnight tonight.
噢 今天不再是女孩之夜了
Oh, it's not another, uh, girls' night out?
不需要了
Doesn't have to be.
- 好的 那么今晚见了 - 好的 回见
- Okay, then. I'll see you tonight. - okay, then.
嘿 你认为这个德古拉真的可以变成蝙蝠吗
Hey, you think this dracula could turn into a bat?
那一点很酷
bat would be cool.
是的
That's right.
是的 和一个埃及人交易
Yeah, an egyptian kind of deal.
不 只是坐在码头那里
No, it was just sitting there on the loading dock.
没有 博士 没有运输票据
No, doctor, there's no shipping invoice.
什么东西都没有
There's no nothing.
你觉得海伦会不会什么记录
You think helen has any record of it in her files?
圣母玛利亚啊
Holy mother of crap!
不
No!
不要
这个石棺可不古老
This sarcophagus isn't ancient.
它来自费城的一个道具仓库
It's from a prop house in philly.
是吗
Well…
那就能解释里面配的这桶干冰了
It goes well with the bucket of dry ice.
他一直是在里面的
He was keeping in it.
这是要帮他制造出他想要的特效
Is he making his own special effects?
正解 一个敬业的木乃伊演员
Yeah, a mummy with a good sense of showmanship.
这真是够傻的
This is stupid.
噢 该死的 杰米 我迟到了
Oh, damn it. jamie. I'm late.
你最好能留在这和木乃伊还有
You're good here with the mummy and the…
这儿疯狂的一切
Crazy …
- 行 - 好
- Yeah. - yeah.
你的损失 联邦警探
Your loss, g-man.
晚上好
Good evening.
我已经远远的注视你很多晚了
I have watched you many nights from afar.
我的激情告诉我没有搞错 米娜
My passion knows no bounds!mina.
你就是爱人的转世
You are the reincarnation of my beloved,
所以我必须拥有你
And I must have you.
噢
Ohh!
玛丽 狗娘养…
Mary, son of a…
杰米
Jamie!
Jamie.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
你不应该说这话
You should not use such language.
在我的新娘面前
In the presence of my bride.
没问题
Okay.
杰米 快跑
Jamie, run!
你现在已经没有机会了 汉克先生
You have no choice in the matter, mr. harker.
米娜是我的
Mina is mine!
嘿 你们还好吗
Hey. you guys all right?
是的 我认为
Yeah, I think so.
而且我还知道了这究竟是怎么回事
And I think I know what's going on.
是吗
Yeah?
它的一部分
Part of it at least.
嗯 这是耳朵
Uh, the ear part?
从德古拉脸上扯下来的 摸摸看
Ripped it off of dracula's head. touch it.
摸起来熟悉吗
Feel familiar to you?
噢 老哥
Oh, man.
道具定型皮肤
The skin of a shapeshifter,
就像圣·路易和雄鹿一样
Just like st. louis and just like milwaukee.
当然 这一个充斥着满满的疯狂
Of course this one's all holding buckets of crazy.
噢 还有
Oh, and, uh…
一定是飞行的时候掉下来的
This must have fallen off during the fight.
看看在带子上的商标
Look at the label on the ribbon.
这是租来的衣服
It's a costume rental.
所有3个怪物
All three monsters …
吸血鬼 狼人还有木乃伊
The dracula, wolf man, and the mummy …
同一个人
All the same critter,
也就意味着我们要找同一个人
Which means we need to catch this freak.
在他变成另外一个怪物前
Before he "creature from the black lagoon's" somebody.
所以你们喜欢莫德和史卡利或其他的（X档案的演员）
So, you guys are like mulder and scully or something,
要么x档案是真的
And the x files are real?
不 x档案是电视剧 这是真的
No, "the x files" is a tv show. this is real.
好的 所以 编剧才能 服装
Okay, so, the stagecraft, the costuming.
感觉想他准备重演
It's like he's trying to reenact.
他最爱的恐怖电影时刻
His favorite monster-movie moments,
接下来是血腥谋杀
Right down to the bloody murders.
等一下 谁是mina
Wait a second. who the hell is mina?
米娜 对
Mina? yeah.
那个叫杰米
That's what he called jamie.
他叫我汉克
And he called me mr. harker.
乔纳森 汉克
Jonathan harker?
他们是电影「小说电影化」里的角色
They're characters from the movies and the novels …
米娜 德古拉的新娘
Mina, dracula's intended bride,
汉克 是第三者
Harker, the fianc that stands in the way.
感觉为你定做的
Seems like he's fixating on you,
他好像把你当他的新娘了
Like he sees you as his bride.
喔 我真幸运
Wow. lucky me.
但盯这你
But to fixate on you,
我猜那变形人以前见过你
My guess is that the shifter has to have seen you before.
或在你周围
Or been around you.
杰米 有没有陌生人来这个镇
Jamie, has anybody strange come to town,
一些对你有特别印象的人
Somebody that has taken a specific notice of you?
我不知道 迪恩 现在是啤酒节
I don't know, dean. it's oktoberfest.
我是调酒师 这里有很多人
I'm a bartender. there's lots of people.
我
I…
等一下 那个爱德华
Wait a second. there is ed.
爱德华 布鲁尔的爱德华
"ed brewer" ed?
对
Yeah.
他大概一个月前搬过来的
He moved here about a month ago.
露西发誓说他爱上我了
Lucy swears he has a crush on me.
我几乎每天晚上都来
He comes in almost every night.
但 你知道 他不是我喜欢的那型
But, you know, I don't think he's the type of guy …
爱德华住那里？
Where does ed live?
我不知道
I don't know.
但他在老影院上班
But he works at the old movie theater.
我想他在那里当放映师
I think he's a projectionist there.
照顾好米娜 好的
Take care of mina? yep.
所以 怪物是真的
So, monsters are real.
一些 是的
Some of them, yeah.
还有那个变形人
And the shapeshifter,
他可以变成不同的人
He can turn into different people.
对的
Yeah.
对的 除非已经变过的
Yeah, except this one's turning.
成为电影节的伟大怪物
Into the great monsters of screenland,
对我来说是新鲜的
Which is a new one for me.
你不是联邦探员 对么？
You're not really fbi, are you?
不是
Not so much.
因此 你是干什么的
So, this is what you do?
你和你的同伴周游全国
You and your partner just tramp across the country.
花自己的钱
On your own dime.
直到你们找到可怕的恶梦来对付
Until you find some horrible nightmare to fight?
某些人付钱的
Some people paying for.
什么
What?
那真糟
That must suck.
我说的是你们为了这些噩梦放弃自己的生活
I mean, you're giving up your life for this terrible…
我不知道 责任感吧
I don't know, responsibility.
过去的几年 我才开始这么想
Last few years, I started thinking that way,
你知道的 给自己点重担
And, uh, you know, it started sort of weighing on me.
当然 那是之前
Of course, that was before…
不久前 我有过
A little while ago, I had this.
那个叫死亡经历
It's called a near-death experience.
非常接近
Very near.
当我醒来
…when I came to…
已经不一样了
There were different.
我的生活不一样了
My life's been different.
我意识到我可以帮助别人
I realize that I help people.
不只是帮助他们 拯救他们
Not just help them, though. I save them.
我猜 这个很酷
I guess it's … it's awesome.
像是一种天赋
It's kind of like a gift…
像使命
Like a mission.
一种上帝给的使命
Kind of like a… a mission from god.
所以 那个让你成为
So, does that make you…
某些僧侣或别的
Some kind of monk or something?
你知道的 独裁者
You know, celibate?
我希望不是
Man, I hope not.
妈的 我的天呐 杰米
Holy crap. oh, my god. jamie.
伙计们 对 对不起
Guys, I'm … I'm sorry.
我还以为你们俩出去了
I thought you guys were going out.
- 露西 - 没事 听着
Lucy, it's … it's okay. uh, listen …
你知道怎么么 我只是回来拿点酒
You know what? I just … I came to borrow a bottle.
我只是拿点东西去
I kind of got something going back at my…
没什么 你们看上去很忙
Anyway, uh, you guys look really busy,
所以我准备消失
So I'm just gonna get out of your hair.
老实说 露西 今晚太疯狂了
Seriously, lucy, it's been a crazy night.
留下来一起喝吧
Stay for a drink.
对，一起吧
Yeah. stay for a drink.
联邦探员 我做了
You, fbi man … what did I …
闭嘴好么 你知道你做了什么
Shut up, okay, you know what you did. what?
我知道你是什么东西
I know what you are.
我什么都不是 我就是在演奏卡西欧电子琴
I'm not anything. I just like to play the casio.
有时间把耳朵张好是吧
Had time to grow the ear back, huh?
什么
What?! ow!
疼
Ow! ow! ow!
耳朵应该掉下来的
It's supposed to come off.
不 不是
No, it's not!
听起来很可怕 杰米 亲爱的你没事吧
Oh, that sounds awful. jamie, honey, are you okay?
恩，我没事
Oh, I am fine.
他连碰都没碰到我
He didn't even touch me.
迪恩来的正是时候把他赶走了
Dean, he just blew right in and fought him off.
其实我不是真的打他
Well, I didn't actually fly,
但我当时确实这么觉得
But I'm sure it seemed that way at the time.
这是真的
It was really, really something.
杰米
Jamie?
迪恩你是黑带或是什么
So, dean, are you like a black belt or what?
当然我认为他们是这样训练你的
Well, I guess they train you.
在理论上是这样战斗的
To fight at the academy or whatever.
迪恩 你这是干什么的
Dean, what are you doing?
是你干的 不是么
It's you, isn't it?
哦 妈的
Oh, damn it!
你在酒里放什么了
What did you put in the drinks?!
没关系 我亲自让你显原形
That's all right. I'll skin you myself.
这场戏
And…scene.
哦 不是吧
Oh, come on.
她很漂亮吧
She is beautiful, no?
第一部的3号新娘
Bride number three from the first film.
她从来没得到她应得的喝彩
She never got the acclaim that she deserved.
也是我选择变成她的形状
Which is why I chose her shape,
用她的外形活动不会被其他人注意到
Her form to move among the mortals unnoticed,
聆听蟋蟀们的生命之曲
To listen to the cricket songs of the living.
在那个时候我发现我的新娘复活了
That is when I discovered my bride had been reborn.
在这个世纪
In this century.
我不会原谅有着南瓜派眼的
I can't get over what a pumpkin-pie-eyed,
畜生你
Crazy son of a bitch you really are.
你不是德古拉 你明白么
You're not dracula. you get that, right?
或者你觉得你是
Or even if you think you are dracula,
那个木乃伊是怎么回事
What the hell's up with the mummy?!
所有的怪物都是我
I am all monsters!
生活不是电影 抱歉你这
Life ain't a movie, you sorry sack of.
哦
Aah.
生命是渺小的
Life is small,
贫乏而有混乱
Meager, messy.
而电影是简单，豪华而有优雅
The movies are grand, simple, elegant.
我选择优雅
I have chosen elegance.
你所谓的优雅只是个词
You think "elegance" is really the word.
是你对玛莉莎和瑞克 迪肯所做的
For what you did to marissa or rick deacon.
或者还有没有其他人
Or any of the others?!
但当然
But of course.
最后这是部恐怖电影
It is a monster movie, after all.
你能意识到会发生什么
You do realize what happens.
在所有恐怖电影的结尾
At the end of every monster movie?
但这部电影我才是编剧
Ah, but this movie is mine.
在这里 怪物是赢家
And in it, the monster wins.
怪物得到美女
The monster gets the girl.
而英雄 被电死
And the hero, he's…electrocuted.
今晚 乔纳森 哈克
And tonight, jonathan harker,
你就是我的英雄
You will be my hero.
等等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
请稍等片刻
Please, excuse me.
晚上好
Good evening.
送匹萨的
Uh…pizza delivery.
你送来我的晚餐了
Ah, you've brought a repast.
太棒了
Excellent.
继续服务他人
Continue to be of such service.
你会觉得你的生活很充实
And your life will be spared.
不错
Uh-huh.
一共15块5
That'll be $15.50.
告诉我
Tell me… yeah?
里面有大蒜么
…is there garlic on this pizza?
我不知道 你有点么
I don't know. did you order garlic?
没有
No!
那就没有
Then no.
听着先生 我还要送4家
Look, mister, I got four other deliveries to make.
请给钱给我 我好走
You want to just pay me the money so I can go?
那当然
Of course. yes.
但我用优惠券
But I have a coupon.
迪恩听着 爱德华不是我们要找的那个
Dean, hey, listen, uh, ed is not our guy.
我猜你和杰米现在在家
Um, I'm guessing you're at home with jamie,
所以给我电话
So just give me a cat1, okay?
露西
Lucy.
你醒了
You wake.
长袍 很适合你
The gown, it suits your beauty.
请穿上
Please, put it on.
我在那里
Where am i?
你对迪恩做什么了
What have you done with dean?
哈克在别的地方休息
Harker is resting elsewhere.
请穿上长袍 你可以用餐了
Please, put on the gown and you may dine.
我们吃匹萨
We are having pizza.
什么
What?
你在发什么疯
What is wrong with you?
露西是你编出来的吧 准备做我的朋友
You made up lucy, right? pretended to be my friend.
我需要知道如果你就是
I needed to know if you were the one.
你可以尝试和别人交谈
You could try talking to people!
来取代你成为这样
But instead you become this?
长袍
The gown.
我不想和你玩这傻游戏
I don't want to play your stupid game, okay?
我只想回家
I just, I just want to go home.
穿上长袍
Put on the gown!
我 我吓到你了
I-i scared you.
你是我最不想吓到的
You were the only one I don't want to scare.
我曾经很喜欢这种电影
I used to love the movies.
他们不是真的
They aren't real.
你不可以当真
You can't make them real.
现实正在孕育
"real" is being born this way.
不同的现实
Different.
现实就是你父亲叫你怪物
"Real" is having your dad call you "monster" …
这是你听到的第一个词
It's the first time you hear the word.
他用铲子想把你打死
And he tries to beat you to death with a shovel.
无论我逃到那里 躲到那里
Everywhere I ran, everywhere I tried to hide,
大家都能找到我 把我挖掘出来 攻击我
People found me, dragged me out and attacked me,
叫我怪胎或怪物
Called me "freak, " called me "monster."
之后我发现了他们
Then I found them.
伟大的怪物
The great monsters.
在他们的电影里 他们是强壮的
In their movies, they were strong.
是可怕的
They were feared.
而又是漂亮的
They were beautiful.
而现在的我就像他们
And now I am like them.
威风凛凛
Commanding.
令人恐惧
Terrifying.
孤独
Lonely.
曾经是这样
Was lonely.
现在我
Now I.
我拥有你
I have you.
我觉得你是不是因为杀了人
Ever think that maybe you're lonely.
才感到孤独
Because you kill people?
或者我孤独才去杀人
Or I kill people because I'm lonely.
你听到了没？
Did you hear that?
什么
What?
迪恩
Dean?
Dean!
谢天谢地 正是时候
Oh, thank god. just in the nick of time.
那家伙要虐待我
That guy was about to frankenstein me.
你好帅哥
Hey there, handsome.
闭嘴
Shut up!
我们走
Let's go.
你永远做不了范海辛
You will never be van helsing!
而你 哈克 死期到了
And you, harker, now you die.
我要是你我就现在闭嘴
How 'bout now you shut the hell up?
银弹
Silver?
杀这个怪胎真是完美
It was beauty that killed the beast.
不要 米娜 不要哭
No, mina, do not weep.
可能这就是为何
Perhaps this is how.
好的 谢谢 帅哥
Well, thank you, g-man.
你为你的国家做了件伟大的事
You have been a great service to your country.
哦 是的 我十分 十分爱国的
Oh, yes, I'm very, very patriotic.
再见
Bye.
你们救了我的命
You guys saved my life, you know?
所以 谢谢
So, thanks.
我喜欢她
I like her.
回归正常感觉真好不是么
Feels good to be back on the job, doesn't it?
对是的
Yeah, it does.
英雄得到美女
The hero gets the girl,
怪物被消灭 一切的一切 完美结局
Monster gets the gank … all in all, happy ending …
一个完美结局 除了
With a happy ending, no less.
真漂亮 迪恩
Real classy, dean.
嘿 我要说的是
Hey, all I'm saying is.
你知道么 那变形人有一点是对的
The shifter man had a point, you know?
要是生活像电影那样简单 那有多好
It would be nice if life was movie simple.
要是我把生活变成电影
Although, if I was turning life into a movie,
我不会演「两傻寻尸记」（1948年电影）这出
I wouldn't do this "abbott and costello meet the monster" crap.
是的 我懂你的想法
Yeah. no, I know what you'd pick.
不 你不知道
No, you don't.
我就是知道
Yeah, I do.
你不知道
No, you don't.
你不知道 小猪2代
You don't."porky's ii."
什么 你听到了
What? you heard me.
狗屎运
Lucky guess.